stats  [-server <inet:hostname:port>] [-user <name>] [-password <password>]
       [-switchserver]
       [-singleseat]
       [-nologo]
       [-production [prompt|silent] [-background]]
       [-symbol <values>]
       [<filename>] ...

To start the application in distributed mode: 

[-server <inet:hostname:port>] The name or IP address and port number 
                               of the server.
                               Example: -server myserver:3016

[-user <name>]                 A valid user name. If a domain name is required,
                               precede the user name with the domain name and a
                               backslash (\).
                               Example: -user "myDomain\myUserName"

[-password <password>]         The user's password.

To start the application and prompt for server login information (Windows
only):

[-switchserver]                Display the "Server Login" dialog box. This
                               switch has precedence over the previous -server,
                               -user, and -password switches.

To start the application in production mode:

[-production [prompt|silent]]  Start the application in production mode. The
                               prompt and silent keywords specify whether to
                               display the dialog that prompts for runtime
                               values if they are specified in the job. The
                               prompt keyword is the default and shows the
                               dialog. The silent keyword suppresses the
                               dialog, in which case you can define the runtime
                               symbols with the -symbol switch. Otherwise, the
                               default value is used.
                               The -switchserver and -singleseat switches are
                               ignored when using -production.
                               Examples: 
                          stats C:\job.spj -production silent -symbol @sex male

To start the application in background production mode:

[-background]                  Run the production job disconnected in the 
                               background on a remote server. You must include
                               the -production switch and must also specify
                               the server using the -server switch.

To start the application in single seat mode:

[-singleseat]                  Start application in a single seat mode.


If none of the previous switches is specified, the application starts in the
default mode.

Other switches:

[-nologo]                      Start the application without displaying the
                               splash screen.

[-symbol <values>]             List of macro symbol-value pairs used in the
                               production job. Each symbol name starts with @.
                               Enclose a value with double quotes if it
                               contains spaces. Rules for including quotes or
                               apostrophes in string literals may vary across
                               operating systems, but enclosing a string that
                               includes single quotes or apostrophes in double
                               quotes usually works (for example, "'a quoted
                               value'").
                               Example:
                               -symbol @sex male @state "North Dakota"

[-unicode [on|off]]            Turn Unicode mode on or off. The default is on.
                               When Unicode mode is off, the application runs
                               in code page mode, which is the current locale
                               encoding. In releases previous to 21, the
                               application started in code page mode.

[<filename>] ...               List of filenames, which can include all
                               application supported file types. Enclose with
                               double quotes if it contains spaces.
                               Example:
                               stats C:\cars.sav C:\analysis.sps

Valid switch qualifiers are a hyphen (-) or double hyphen (--). You can also
use a forward slash (/) on Windows platforms. If a parameter is not preceded by
a switch qualifier or a valid argument, it is treated as a filename. 


